{"data":[{"question":"Even the most discriminating gourmet will agree that food in the south is as good as any other region in the country.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"despite greater ","b":"material output","c":"the people in the year 2,000 ","d":"it is today","answer":"4","explain":"- It is today-> they are today","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Some scientists predict that, despite greater material output, the people in the year 2,000 will be poorer in many ways than it is today.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"approaches ","b":"the Earth ","c":"any other ","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"- Is-> does","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Venus approaches the Earth more closely than any other planet is.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"type ","b":"mixture ","c":"but ","d":"tinted","answer":"3","explain":"- But-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Tempera, a type of paint, is prepared from a mixture of water, egg yolk, and one but more tinted powders.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"outstanding ","b":"catch ","c":"her to his ","d":"advisory committee ","answer":"2","explain":"- Catch-> caught","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Over forty years ago, Helen Hall's outstanding contributions as a settlement organizer catch the attention of president Franklin Roosevelt, who appointed her to his advisory committee on economic security.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Part of ","b":"strikes ","c":"a rest ","d":"ground","answer":"3","explain":"- A rest-> the rest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Part of the sunlight that strikes the Earth is reflected into the sky, and a rest is absorbed by the ground.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"hadn't ","b":"worthwhile ","c":"with ","d":"for ","answer":"1","explain":"- Hadn't-> had","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"It seemed as if I hadn't scarcely done anything worthwhile with my time, for I failed three courses.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"use all ","b":"of ","c":"its vacation time","d":"never takes a vacation himself","answer":"3","explain":"- Its vacation time-> their vacation time","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"The office manager insists that his staff use all of its vacation time, but he hardly never takes a  vacation himself\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"before ","b":"to ","c":"can ","d":"even ","answer":"1","explain":"- Before-> previously","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Life insurance, before available only to young, healthy persons, can now be obtained for old people and even for pets.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"originating ","b":"deep ","c":"some ","d":"considerable rigidity","answer":"2","explain":"- Deep-> depth","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Moonquakes originating at deep of some 800 kilometers indicate the Moon has considerable rigidity and is not molten at such levels.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"possesses a wealth ","b":"of evidence ","c":"arose from lower ","d":"time long period","answer":"4","explain":"- Time long period-> long time period","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}